let quiz = [
  {
    question: "Many teachers always  ____________ much homework.",
    option: ["Give", "Gives", "Are give", "Is give"],
    answer: 1,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "They_________ look at me everyday",
    option: ["Does", "Doesn't", "Aren't", "Don't"],
    answer: 4,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "_______ your grandparent let you go to bed late?",
    option: ["Are", "Does", "Is", "Do"],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "________ my father wait for you every affternoon?",
    option: ["Do", "Does", "Will", "Is"],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "She_______ a movie everyday.",
    option: ["Watch", "Watches", "Watching", "Watchs"],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "He doesn't _______ breakfast at my home.",
    option: ["Eats", "Eating", "Eat", "Ate"],
    answer: 3,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Does_____ love my cat?",
    option: ["She", "We", "I", "all firends"],
    answer: 1,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Do ______ my father?",
    option: ["She hates", "You hate ", "My mother hating", "My friend love"],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "She ____ a book to my room?",
    option: ["Brings", "Bringing", "Bring", "Is bring"],
    answer: 1,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "They _____ to school?",
    option: ["Don't go", "Don't be going", "Doesn't go", "Is going"],
    answer: 1,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Kalimat (-) dari kalimat 'Dia perempuan membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
    option:[],
    answer: "She doesn't buy vegetables in market",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Kalimat (?) dari kalimat 'Dia perempuan membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
    option: [
      "Do I buy vegetables in market?",
      "Does she buy vegetables in market?",
      "Do he buy vegetables in market?",
      "Does he buy vegetables in market?",
    ],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Kalimat (+) dari kalimat 'Dia laki-laki tidak membeli sayur di pasar' adalah",
    option: [
      "I buy vegetables in market",
      "She buy vegetables in market",
      "He buys vegetables in market",
      "He buys vegetables in market",
    ],
    answer: 4,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Mereka membawaku ke rumahmu",
    option: [],
    answer: "They bring me to your home",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Saya tidak meninggalkan mereka di sungai",
    option: [],
    answer: "I don't leave them in the river",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
    option: [
      "They look at I in my room",
      "I see their in a room",
      "They need me everyday",
      "Me love you",
    ],
    answer: 3,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
    option: [
      "Theirs house looks messy",
      "Theirs are mine",
      "Mine is your",
      "Them I love their room",
    ],
    answer: 3,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'ruangan mereka sangat kecil'",
    option: [],
    answer: "Their room is so small",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
    option: [
      "Do she look good?",
      "Do you lovers me?",
      "Does she type in my computer?",
      "Does my grandparents die?",
    ],
    answer: 3,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Manakah kalimat yang benar di bawah ini",
    option: [
      "I don't links it to my friend?",
      "It doesn't suit me",
      "Does she brings in my computer?",
      "Do my grandparents dies at hotel?",
    ],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Saya akan dirumah nanti malam'",
    option: [],
    answer: "I will be at home tonight",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Saya tidak sedang memikirkan mu'",
    option: [],
    answer: "I am not thinking about you",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "I _______ not bringing umbrella now",
    option: ["Am","Is","Do","Does" ],
    answer: 1,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "I _______ be an umbrella next year",
    option: ["Am","Wish","Will not","Does not" ],
    answer: 3,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Sedangkah bapakmu bersama ibumu?'",
    option: [],
    answer: "Is your father with your mother?",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Saya sedang di kantor'",
    option: [],
    answer: "I am at office",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Akankah saya mengunjungimu?'",
    option: [],
    answer: "Will i visit you?",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Mereka menerima uang dari ibumu'",
    option: [],
    answer: "They receive money from your mother",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {
    question: "Translate kalimat ini'Dia laki-laki tidak sedang belajar'",
    option: [],
    answer: "He is not studying",
    type: "isian",
  },
  {question: "I am not ________ you",
    option: ["Sees","Seeing","See","Saw" ],
    answer: 2,
    type: "pilihan-ganda",
  },
  
  
];
